Robert E. Lee Papers WLU.Coll.0064
Washington and Lee University, University Library Special Collections and Archives
- Letters to and about Robert E. Lee, 1837-1870 (Box 7-12A)
  - Letters to and about Robert E. Lee, 1866-02-01-1866-05-31 (Box 7A, Folder 36-63)
    - Correspondences, 1866-05-01-1866-05-04 (Box 7A, Folder 57)
      - Stonewall Literary Society to Robert E. Lee, 1866-05-01 (Box 7A, Folder 57)
        This letter by members of the Stonewall Literary Society is for Robert E. Lee. The society writes to Lee that they have decided to make him an honorary member for his actions at the Siege of Petersburg, Virginia during the American Civil War.
        Literature -- Societies, etc.; Virginia--Petersburg; Lee, Robert E. (Robert Edward), 1807-1870; Bishop, Carter Richard, 1849-1941; Jones, Edward B.; Scott, G. W.; Baugh, James, d. 1877; Jackson, Stonewall, 1824-1863; Stonewall Literary Society
      - Richard Pennefather Rothwell, 1866-05-02 (Box 7A, Folder 57)
        This letter by Richard Pennefather Rothwell is to Robert E. Lee. Rothwell has heard that Washington College is increasing its staff and offers his services as a professor. He offers to be a professor of mining, metallurgy, mineralogy, or geology.
        Mining schools and education; Geology; Mining engineering; Mineralogy; Metallurgy; Lee, Robert E. (Robert Edward), 1807-1870; Rothwell, Richard P. (Richard Pennefather), 1836-1901; Washington College (Lexington, Va.); Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute; École nationale supérieure des mines de Paris
      - Robert V. Richardson to Robert E. Lee, 1866-05-02; Richardson, Robert V., 1820-1870 (Box 7A, Folder 57)
        This letter by Robert Vinkler Richardson is for Robert E. Lee. Richardson is trying to establish foreign investment in the southern American cotton industry. This letter is written on a circular sent out to different cotton planters, with this one having a hand-written letter for Lee.
        Cotton; Investments, Foreign; Lee, Robert E. (Robert Edward), 1807-1870; H. Myers & Co.; Reneau, N. S.; Messers. Bellot des Miniers, Bros. & Co.; Confederate States of America. Army. Cavalry
      - Thomas Roberts Slicer to Robert E. Lee, 1866-05-02; Slicer, Thomas Roberts, 1847-1916 (Box 7A, Folder 57)
        This letter by Thomas Roberts Slicer is addressed to Robert E. Lee. Slicer, the son of Lee's friend Henry Slicer, inquires about a position to teach elocution at Washington College.
        Elocution -- Study and teaching; Lee, Robert E. (Robert Edward), 1807-1870; Slicer, Henry, 1801-1874
      - Daniel F. Wright to Robert E. Lee, 1866-05-02; Wright, Daniel F. (Box 7A, Folder 57)
        This letter by Daniel F. Wright is addressed to Robert E. Lee. Wright asks for a circular of Washington College to give a potential student he knows. He also mentions that he was a surgeon in Archer's Brigade during the American Civil War.
        Lee, Robert E. (Robert Edward), 1807-1870; Washington College (Lexington, Va.); Confederate States of America. Army. Tennessee Brigade
      - James Cleland to Robert E. Lee, 1866-05-04
        This letter by James Cleland is addressed to Robert E. Lee. Cleland, a plumber and gas-fitter in Lynchburg, offers his services to Washington College to install a gas system. Included with this letter is a pamphlet from the Automatic Gas Company of Baltimore advertising their product.
        Gas-fitting; Plumbing; Lee, Robert E. (Robert Edward), 1807-1870; Washington College (Lexington, Va.); Automatic Gas Company of Baltimore; Kirkpatrick, Thomas J. (Jellis), 1829-1897
      - J. C. Parks to Robert E. Lee, 1866-05-04 (Box 7A, Folder 57)
        This letter by J. C. Parks is addressed to Robert E. Lee. Parks asks Lee if he and "Mr. Frazier" may be the publishers of Lee's American Civil War history in the southern states. Their conditions are that they would liberally compensate Lee and that half of the profits be given to widows and orphans of fallen Confederate soldiers. They list Casper Bell, John Bullock Clark, and John Heagan as references.
        Publishing; Missouri--Rocheport; Lee, Robert E. (Robert Edward), 1807-1870; Confederate States of America. Army; Frazier; Bell, Caspar Wistar, 1819-1898; Confederate States of America. Congress.; Heagan, John; United States. Congress; Clark, John B. (John Bullock), 1802-1885
      - Warren S. Barlow to Robert E. Lee, 1866-05-04; Barlow, Warren S. (Box 7A, Folder 57)
        This letter by Warren S. Barlow is addressed to Robert E. Lee. Barlow writes that Lee's portrait by Elijah C. Middleton has been finished. He will send it by express to "Mr. Lutz" for Lee to receive.
        Portraits; Portrait prints; Lithography; Chromolithography; Chromolithography, Victorian; Lee, Robert E. (Robert Edward), 1807-1870; Middleton, Elijah C.; Lutz family
    - Correspondences, 1866-05-05-1866-05-09 (Box 7A, Folder 58)
      - Simon Bolivar Buckner to Robert E. Lee, 1866-05-05; Buckner, Simon Bolivar, 1823-1914 (Box 7A, Folder 58)
        This letter by Simon Bolivar Buckner is addressed to Robert E. Lee. Buckner introduces a student of Washington College he knows, J. Esten Cooke. Buckner also tells Lee that he is currently in New Orleans working as an editor for a paper.
        Lee, Robert E. (Robert Edward), 1807-1870; Cooke, J. Esten, Jr.; Confederate States of America. Army
      - Charles B. Richardson to Robert E. Lee, 1866-05-05; Richardson, Charles B. (Box 7A, Folder 58)
        This letter by Charles B. Richardson is addressed to Robert E. Lee. Enclosed with this letter was a map of the Potomac Army that Lee requested, as well as John Beauchamp Jones' "A Rebel War Clerk's Diary" for ideas. Along with this package, Richardson updates Lee on the publishing of Henry Lee III's memoirs. Richardson also tells Lee that he is going through some financial setbacks but that it shouldn't hinder his business.
        Publishing; Map publishing; Lee, Robert E. (Robert Edward), 1807-1870; United States. Army of the Potomac; Jones, J. B. (John Beauchamp), 1810-1866; Wynne, Charles H., 1822-1870; Lee, Henry, 1756-1818
      - Ancrum B. Burr to Robert E. Lee, 1866-05-06; Burr, Ancrum B. (Box 7A, Folder 58)
        This letter by Ancrum B. Burr is addressed to Robert E. Lee. She wishes for her son, Edward Johnston, to attend Washington College and would like a circular. Burr also says that Edward's father may have graduated from the United States Military Academy around the same time as Lee, but that he died in the Mexican-American War.
        Lee, Robert E. (Robert Edward), 1807-1870; Washington College (Lexington, Va.); Johnston, Edward; Johnston, B. W.; United States Military Academy
      - John Mimms and Edwin O'Brien to Robert E. Lee, 1866-05-06; Mimms, John; O'Brien, Edwin (Box 7A, Folder 58)
        This letter by John Mimms and Edwin O'Brien is addressed to Robert E. Lee. They say that several students in their town wish to attend Washington College and would like a catalogue.
        Kentucky--Hadensville; Lee, Robert E. (Robert Edward), 1807-1870; Washington College (Lexington, Va.)
      - Richmond Light Infantry Blues to Robert E. Lee, 1866-05-07; Levy, Ezekiel Jacob, 1833-1908; Jarvis, George William, 1832-1913; DePriest, Emmett E., 1842-1903 (Box 7A, Folder 58)
        This letter by members of the Richmond Light Infantry Blues is addressed to Robert E. Lee. The militia group is celebrating its seventy-third anniversary on May 10, 1866 and is inviting Lee to celebrate.
        Virginia--Richmond--Exchange Hotel; Lee, Robert E. (Robert Edward), 1807-1870; Virginia. Militia. Richmond Light Infantry Blues
      - Houston Rucker to Robert E. Lee, 1866-05-08; Rucker, Houston, 1835-1911 (Box 7A, Folder 58)
        This letter by Houston Rucker is addressed to Robert E. Lee. Rucker writes that he would like a circular and information on Washington College to send a friend's son.
      - Seaton Gales to Robert E. Lee, 1866-05-08; Gales, Seaton, 1828-1878 (Box 7A, Folder 58)
        This letter by Seaton Gales is addressed to Robert E. Lee. Gales, an editor of the Raleigh Sentinel (N.C.) newspaper, offers to help identify a publisher for Lee's proposed book on the American Civil War. Gales included a copy of the Raleigh Sentinel with the letter. At the end of the letter Gales notes that he was an Assistant Adjutant General under General Stephen Dodson Ramseur
        Raleigh Sentinel Newspaper; Ramseur, Stephen Dodson, 1837-1864
      - George Dawes Appleton to Robert E. Lee, 1866-05-08; Appleton, George Dawes, 1818-1890 (Box 7A, Folder 58)
        This letter by George Dawes Appleton is addressed to Robert E. Lee. Dawes writes that he wants to admit his son to Washington College and would like information about attending.
        Appleton, George Hough, 1854-1930
      - John T. Adkisson to Robert E. Lee, 1866-05-08; Adkisson, John T., 1841-1880 (Box 7A, Folder 58)
        Adkisson, who had attended Dolbear Commercial College in New Orleans, La., inquires about continuing his education at Washington College and offers a plan for how he may be able to afford it. He notes that he served in a Texas Brigade during the American Civil War.
        Confederate States of America. Army. Texas Brigade; Dolbear Commercial College
      - James F. Dumble to Robert E. Lee, 1866-05-09; Dumble, James F., 1829-1911 (Box 7A, Folder 58)
        This letter by James F. Dumble is addressed to Robert E. Lee. Dumble wants to send his son, around fifteen years of age, to Washington College and would like to know the terms of entering. He also asks if his son can board with a family.
        Lee, Robert E. (Robert Edward), 1807-1870; Washington College (Lexington, Va.); Dumble, E. T. (Edwin Theodore), 1852-1927
    - Correspondences, 1866-05-10-1866-05-14 (Box 7A, Folder 59)
      - Reverend William Norvell Ward to Robert E. Lee, 1866-05-10; Ward, William Norvell, Reverend, 1805-1881 (Box 7A, Folder 59)
        This letter by Reverend William Norvell Ward is addressed to Robert E. Lee. Ward wants to know if Lee would like a photographic copy of a painting by Mattie Ward, his daughter. The subject of this painting is Stratford Hall, Lee's birthplace.
        Virginia--Bladensfield; Virginia--Stratford Hall; Painting; Lee, Robert E. (Robert Edward), 1807-1870; Ward, Mattie
      - J. F. Heun to Robert E. Lee, 1866-05-11; Heun, J. F. (Box 7A, Folder 59)
        This letter by J. F. Heun is addressed to Robert E. Lee. Heun asks Lee for an autographed wartime document.
        Autographs
      - W. H. Nettleton to Robert E. Lee, 1866-05-11; Nettleton, W. H. (Box 7A, Folder 59)
        This letter by W. H. Nettleton is addressed to Robert E. Lee. Nettleton, an Englishman having traveled the county over the past year, writes that he would like a hand-written line or two from Lee as a souvenir of this trip.
        Autographs; Lee, Robert E. (Robert Edward), 1807-1870
      - Josiah Warren to Robert E. Lee, 1866-05-12; Warren, Josiah (Box 7A, Folder 59)
        This letter by Josiah Warren is addressed to Robert E. Lee. This letter accompanied a book Warren wanted Lee to read.
        Philosophy; Lee, Robert E. (Robert Edward), 1807-1870
      - Horatio Richardson Moore to Robert E. Lee, 1866-05-12; Moore, Horatio Richardson, 1833-1926 (Box 7A, Folder 59)
        This letter by Horatio Richardson Moore is addressed to Robert E. Lee. Moore asks if it would be okay for some acquaintances in New Orleans to use Lee's name in their company.
        Lee, Robert E. (Robert Edward), 1807-1870
      - William T. Somervell to Robert E. Lee, 1866-05-12; Somervell, William T., 1846-1920 (Box 7A, Folder 59)
        This letter by William T. Somervell is addressed to Robert E. Lee. Somervell wishes to attend Washington College and asks for a circular, terms, and regulations for applying.
      - Mansfield Lovell to Robert E. Lee, 1866-05-13; Lovell, Mansfield, 1822-1884 (Box 7A, Folder 59)
        This letter by Mansfield Lovell is addressed to Robert E. Lee. Having heard that Lee is writing a history of the American Civil War, Lovell offers a list of documents from Confederate officers in his possession for Lee to borrow from. Mansfield notes his documents of evidence taken by the Joint Congressional Committee on the affairs of the Confederate Naval Department, and correspondence between the Confederate States of America War Department and General Lafayette McLaws concerning the fate of New Orleans, Louisiana.
        Lee, Robert E. (Robert Edward), 1807-1870; Confederate States of America. Navy; McLaws, Lafayette, 1821-1897; Confederate States of America. War Department
      - Robert Lewis Dabney to Robert E. Lee, 1866-05-14; Dabney, Robert Lewis, 1820-1898 (Box 7A, Folder 59)
        This letter by Robert Lewis Dabney is addressed to Robert E. Lee. Dabney writes that an advertisement of his Stonewall Jackson biography gives credit of Lee's review and revisions to the publisher instead. He explains to Lee that the publisher decided to do this, not him.
        Biography; Publishing; Advertising; Lee, Robert E. (Robert Edward), 1807-1870; Jackson, Stonewall, 1824-1863; Blelock & Co
      - Lizzie C. Hull to Robert E. Lee, 1866-05-14; Hull, Lizzie C. (Box 7A, Folder 59)
        This letter by Lizzie C. Hull is addressed to Robert E. Lee. She acknowledges the receipt that her son cannot attend Washington College and wishes the best for Lee.
      - Jeannette Ritchie Hadermann Walworth to Robert E. Lee, 1866-05-14; Walworth, Jeannette H., 1837-1918 (Box 7A, Folder 59)
        This letter by Jeannette Ritchie Hadermann Walworth is addressed to Robert E. Lee. She asks for a piece of Lee's hair for her nephew who is also named Lee in honor of him.
    - Correspondences, 1866-05-15-1866-05-17 (Box 7A, Folder 60)
      - Jubal Anderson Early to Robert E. Lee, 1866-05-15; Early, Jubal Anderson, 1816-1894 (Box 7A, Folder 60)
        Jubal Early recounts his participation in battles of the American Civil War and describes his experience living in Mexico since the Confederate surrender and his planned move to Canada.
        The original envelope is included with this letter.
        Lee, Robert E. (Robert Edward), 1807-1870; Confederate States of America. Army of Northern Virginia. Early's Division; Confederate States of America. Army of Northern Virginia. Corps, 3rd; Confederate States of America. Army of Northern Virginia. Corps, 2nd; Johnson, Edward, 1816-1873; Hotchkiss, Jedediah, 1828-1899; Hunter, David, 1802-1886; Sheridan, Philip Henry, 1831-1888; Magruder, John Bankhead, 1807-1871; Letcher, John, 1813-1884
      - Aaron Howell Pierson Sr. to Robert E. Lee, 1866-05-15; Pierson, Aaron Howell, Sr., 1810-1875 (Box 7A, Folder 60)
        This letter by Aaron Howell Pierson Sr. is addressed to Robert E. Lee. Pierson wishes to send his son to Washington College but does not know the requirements. Pierson worries that because of his son's service in the American Civil War, he may be too far behind his studies to attend.
        Lee, Robert E. (Robert Edward), 1807-1870; Washington College (Lexington, Va.); Pierson, Aaron Howell, Jr., 1847-1921
      - James Dabney McCabe to Robert E. Lee, 1866-05-15; McCabe, James D., 1842-1883 (Box 7A, Folder 60)
        This letter by James Dabney McCabe is addressed to Robert E. Lee. McCabe asks if he can write a narration of Lee's actions during the American Civil War. He notes that as an ex-cadet of Virginia Military Institue, he published "A Life of Lieut. Gen. T. J. Jackson" during the war.
        Lee, Robert E. (Robert Edward), 1807-1870; Jackson, Stonewall, 1824-1863; Virginia Military Institute
      - R. Thompson to Robert E. Lee, 1866-05-15; Thompson, R. (Box 7A, Folder 60)
        This letter by R. Thompson is addressed to Robert E. Lee. Thompson offers to publish a British edition of Lee's planned book on the American Civil War. Lee never wrote the book.
        Publishing; Publishers and publishing--International cooperation; Lee, Robert E. (Robert Edward), 1807-1870; John Murray (Firm); Longman (Firm)
      - Sam Beach Jones to Robert E. Lee, 1866-05-15; Jones, Samuel Beach, Rev., 1811-1883 (Box 7A, Folder 60)
        This letter by the Reverend Samuel Beach Jones is addressed to Robert E. Lee, updating him on events. Jones has found the whereabouts of a painting taken from Lee's Arlington house. Jones also found another painting of a winter scene but doesn't know for sure that it belonged to Lee. Along with these paintings, Jones has come across a book that supposedly comes from Lee's library but is marked as belonging to Charles A. Atkinson. Along with these matters, Jones says that he is taking a trip to Europe and offers to collect money for Washington College.
        Arlington House, the Robert E. Lee Memorial (Va.); Lee, Robert E. (Robert Edward), 1807-1870; Lewis, Robert W., Jr., 1839-1920; Atkinson, Charles A.; Freemantle, Arthur James Lyon, Sir, 1835-1901; Stuart, J.E.B. (James Ewell Brown), 1833-1864; Reed, William B. (William Bradford), 1806-1876; Stephens, Alexander H. (Alexander Hamilton), 1812-1883
      - John Speck LeFevre to Robert E. Lee, 1866-05-16; LaFever, John Speck, 1848-1888 (Box 7A, Folder 60)
        This letter by John Speck LaFever is addressed to Robert E. Lee. LaFever asks for information to attend Washington College.
      - Dr. Wesley Emmett Gatwood to Robert E. Lee, 1866-05-17; Gatwood, Wesley Emmett, Dr., 1845-1924 (Box 7A, Folder 60)
        This letter by Dr. Wesley Emmett Gatewood is addressed to Robert E. Lee. Gatewood would like information on attending Washington College and a piece of clothing Lee wore during the American Civil War.
      - Augustus Machim Garber to Robert E. Lee, 1866-05-17; Garber, Augustus Machim, ca.1811-d.1890 (Box 7A, Folder 60)
        This letter by Augustus Machim Garber is addressed to Robert E. Lee. He writes that he has sent catalogues of Washington College to his uncle. However, his uncle would like information on fees and payment to the school. Garber also mentions sculptor William Rudolph O'Donovan and shares that the scultpor, with approval from Lee, will continue workingon a bust of Stonwall Jackson.
        Originally included with this letter was a photograph of O'Donovan's bust of Stonewall Jackson.
        Sculpture; Busts; Statues; Lee, Robert E. (Robert Edward), 1807-1870; Washington College (Lexington, Va.); O'Donovan, William Rudolph, 1844-1920; Confederate States of America. Army. Staunton Artillery; Jackson, Stonewall, 1824-1863
      - C. Williams to Robert E. Lee, 1866-05-17; Williams, C. (Box 7A, Folder 60)
        This letter by C. Williams is addressed to Robert E. Lee on behalf of the Great Southern and Western Life and Accident Insurance Company announcing a forthcoming shareholders meeting.
        Insurance; Fire insurance; Marine insurance; Life insurance; Accident insurance; Great Southern and Western Life and Accident Insurance Company
    - Correspondences, 1866-05-18-1866-05-23 (Box 7A, Folder 61)
    - Correspondences, 1866-05-24-1866-05-26 (Box 7A, Folder 62)
    - Correspondences, 1866-05-27-1866-05-31 (Box 7A, Folder 63)
  - Letters to and about Robert E. Lee (Box 8, Folder 64-96)
    - Correspondences, 1866-06-01 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - Correspondences, 1866-06-02-1866-06-04 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - Correspondences, 1866-06-05-1866-06-10 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - Correspondences, 1866-06-11-1866-06-12 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - Correspondences, 1866-06-13-1866-06-15 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - Correspondences, 1866-06-16-1866-06-20 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - Correspondences, 1866-06-21 (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - Correspondences, 1866-06-22 (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - Correspondences, 1866-06-23-1866-06-26 (Box 8, Folder 72)
    - Correspondences, 1866-06-27-1866-06-30 (Box 8, Folder 73)
    - Correspondences, 1866-07-02-1866-07-04 (Box 8, Folder 74)
    - Correspondences, 1866-07-05-1866-07-06 (Box 8, Folder 75)
    - Correspondences, 1866-07-07-1866-07-09 (Box 8, Folder 76)
    - Sister Mary B. Linton to Robert E. Lee, 1866-07-10; Linton, Mary B. (Mary Baptista), Sister, 1822-1901 (Box 8, Folder 77)
      Sister Mary Baptista Linton asks Robert E. Lee to speak at Mount de Chental Visitation Academy. Because of the event, the academy sent materials to Washington and Lee University archives. This includes a booklet from the one-hundred and fiftieth anniversary of the school with a quote from Robert E. Lee on the front. Along with this are materials from the Georgetown Academy of the Visitation on Sister Baptista, a scan of Lee's letter to Sister Baptista, and a section of Mount de Chental's centennial booklet on its southern fund.
      Mount de Chental Visitation Academy
    - Correspondences, 1866-07-10 (Box 8, Folder 78)
      This folder contains two original letters from Mercer University faculty, and photographic reproductions made in 1944 from negatives taken by Michael Miley
      Mercer University; Miley, Michael, 1841-1918
    - Correspondences, 1866-07-11-1866-07-13 (Box 8, Folder 79)
    - Correspondences, 1866-07-14-1866-07-15 (Box 8, Folder 80)
      - Frederick A. P. Barnard to Robert E. Lee, 1866-07-14; Barnard, Frederick A. P. (Frederick Augustus Porter), 1809-1889 (Box 8, Folder 80)
        Frederick A. P. Barnard sends Robert E. Lee a recommendation for Robert B. White, D. D. to be chair of mental and moral philosophy at Washington College. This letter is sent to Lee in two parts: an introduction and the recommendation itself.
        White, Robert B., D. D., ca.1817-ca.1882
      - Charles P. Stone to Robert E. Lee, 1866-07-17; Stone, Charles Pomeroy, 1824-1887 (Box 8, Folder 80)
        Chas. P. Stone offers coal from Dover Mines, a coal mining comapny in Goochland, Virginia for Washington College.
        Dover Mines
      - Lafayette Guild to Robert E. Lee, 1866-07-14; Guild, Lafayette, 1825-1870 (Box 8, Folder 80)
        Lafayette Guild introduces Robert E. Lee to William G. Cochrane, a new Washington College student. He also says that he has been keeping in touch with Walter H. Stevens in Mexico.
        Cochrane, William G. (William Gilbert) "Gilly", 1848-1913; Stevens, W. H. (Walter H.)
      - Burr Harrison McCown to Robert E. Lee, 1866-07-14; McCown, B. H. (Burr Harrison), 1806-1881 (Box 8, Folder 80)
        Burr Harrison McCown asks Robert E. Lee for two catalogues of Washington College. One for him, and one for Joseph Henry in Leavenworth, Kansas.
        Henry, Joseph, b. ca. 1847
      - J. B. Moore to Robert E. Lee, 1866-07-14; Moore, J. B., b. ca. 1847 (Box 8, Folder 80)
        J. B. Moore asks Robert E. Lee for a catalogue of Washington College.
      - J. Hewett to Robert E. Lee, 1866-07-14; Hewett, J. (Box 8, Folder 80)
        J. Hewett offers to hire Robert E. Lee as superintendent of Natchez Institute.
        Natchez Institute
      - Aaron Howell Pierson Sr. to Robert E. Lee, 1866-07-14; Pierson, Aaron Howell, Sr., 1810-1875 (Box 8, Folder 80)
        Aaron Howell Pierson Sr. tells Robert E. Lee he has received his letter in the mail and his son, Aaron Howell Pierson Jr., needs to attend preparatory school.
        Pierson, Aaron Howell, Jr., 1847-1921
      - James Patterson Rogers to Robert E. Lee, 1866-07-15; Rogers, James P. (James Patterson), 1839-1904 (Box 8, Folder 80)
        James Patterson Rogers contacts Robert E. Lee, representing Lieutenant Samuel S. Mathers. Lieutenant Mathers wishes to return a letter by George Washington addressed to the board of trustees of Washington College. Mathers gained this letter during Hunter's Raid in the American Civil War.
        Separated Materials
        This item is housed in the secure file.
        Samuel S. Mathers' direct letter to Robert E. Lee, dated 1866-07-30, is also located in the secure file.
        Hunter's Raid (Lexington, Virginia: 1864); Mathers, Samuel S., Lieutenant, b. ca. 1840; Washington, George, 1732-1799